<help popup="yes">
Welcome to my server.
Below is a categorised description of all the plugins currently installed.


#### HANDLING ####
AllWheels - plugin for changing wheels.
/wheels [default|offroad] - changes wheels.


#### VISIBILITY ####
carhider - a resource to hide/unhide your fellow racers.
/carhide - toggle for the resource to do its thing.

carfade - a resource to "fade" your fellow racers.
/carfade - toggle for the resource to do its thing.

time - a resource for changing the time of day client side. Note: this resource also resets weather if the weather ID exceeds 20.
/day - sets time to 12.
/night - sets the time to 24.
/day [auto] - sets time to 12 automatically at the start of each map.
/night [auto] - sets the time to 24 automatically at the start of each map.

#### UI ####
race_delay_indicator - a resource that shows you some time comparisons.
/cpdelays 	   - toggle the resource on and off.
/setdelaypos [x y] - change the text position.

race_traffic_sensor - displays arrows on screen pointing to nearby race traffic. By default it is hidden with carhide enabled. Use the "always" option to bypass this.
/trafficsensor - toggle for the resource to do its thing.
/trafficsensor [always] - always show the sensor.

yuyu-speedometer - a "digital" speedometer resource based on blue-speedometer and nos2.
/speedometer [off|on] 	 - hides/unhides the speedometer.
/reset_speedometer 	 - resets the speedometer to its default configuration.
/move_speedometer 	 - allows you to change the speedometer's position on the screen using the mouse.
/scale_speedometer [number] - lets you change the size of the speedometer. It is a multiplier. The defualt value is 1.
/font_speedometer [fontname|leave blank for a list of options] - lets you change the font the speedometer is using.

race_nos3 - a commonly used nos resource, somewhat modified for this server.
/nos [normal|nfs|hybrid] - sets nos firing style.
/nossustain [off|off] 	 - no clue.
/nosgauge [off|on] 	 - hides/unhides the nos gauge.
/reset_nosgauge 	 - resets the nos gauge to its default configuration.
/move_nosgauge 		 - allows you to change the position of the nos gauge's position on the screen using the mouse.
/scale_nosgauge 	 - to be implemented.


#### PERSONALISATION ####
carcolorpicker - a resource to color your car with.
/color - open the color picker's menu.

skins_selector - a resource to change your character's skin.
/skin [id] - changes your skin to the specified id.


#### MISC ####
race_league - a resource for managing clan wars.
/r     - announce that your team is ready (team captains only).
/f     - announce that you want to redo the current round (team captains only).
/haha  - make fun of the enemy team (team captains only).
/gg    - gg (team captains only).
/newtr - start a new match (admins only).
/endtr - end the current match (admins only).
/fun   - set the current round to be a fun round (admins only).

randomcwmapfilter - starts a random map from a predefined filter. You can change the filter by doubleclicking on the resource in the admin panel.
/randomcw - picks a map (admins only).

ghost - a recorded ghost of the fastest drive on any given map.
/toggleghost - toggle to hide/unhide the ghost driver.
/deleteghost - delete ghost (admins only)

car_radio_system - a radio resource that allows online streaming. Make sure you allow your MTA settings to output custom sounds if you wish to hear the radio.
/radio - enables or disables the radio.

one_spawn - self explanatory.

removerandomobjects - self explanatory.

bridgefix - fixes collisions on the infamous "red bridge".
</help>
